rn.org 2016-12-25

# Online Nursing Continuing Education Provider with a Free Online CE Course

| 

|    
---|---  

|    

|    

|    

|    

|    

|    
  
_"So easy to navigate the website. Very interesting courses and informative! RN.ORG is my source for nurse CEUs! ", Susan C., RN, Warsaw, IN_

_"Excellent Nursing CEU Provider! Thank you. Very well written. This was easy to read and was presented very well. The online free nursing education course is excellent ", Robert E., RN, CEN, San Diego, CA_

_"Wow, your system is so cool. I was looking for CEU Continuing Education Free Nursing and found RN.ORG! I enjoy the ability to reprint my certificates and review my transcript at any time", Tony G., ANRP, Clinical Instructor, Miami, FL_

_"I was looking for a Education Nursing Online Provider and came upon RN.ORG!! Great information for the nurse as well for teaching our youth", Martha W., RN, Toronto, ON_

_"Very good source for Online Nursing Education and Nursing Contact Hours.. The content is something that all parents and healthcare workers can use", Rachelle U., LPN, Key Largo, FL_

_"Excellent, Thanks for the Free Online CE Course! You have become my Online RN Continuing Education Provider! I have since contacted my friends and now the whole floor is on RN.ORG! Learning with www.rn.org is so easy. I never knew taking nursing continuing education courses to obtain RN CEUs could be so easy", Ronald G., RN, Washington, DC_

_"$20 Unlimited Nursing/Disaster/FEMA CEUs really caught my attention!! Online Disaster & FEMA Courses for Nurses, Medics, EMTs and MDs is exactly what we need over here in Iraq!", Robin K., RN, US Army_

_"Excellent Free Nursing CEU Provider! Amazing, Nursing CEU's Free brought up RN.ORG immediately! Thank you. Very well written. This was easy to read and was presented very well. The online free nursing education ceu's are excellent ", Robert E., RN, CEN, San Diego, CA_

_"I was looking in RN Magazines and Medceu org to learn about FEMA, Disaster and Bioterrorism and your site is excellent", Willam K., RN, Toledo, OH_

_"Your Bioterrorism for ER course is outstanding and covers what we need to know to keep our ER safe", Steven S., RN, South Bend, IN_

_"$20 Unlimited Nurses CE caught my attention however FEMA, Disaster and Nursing Online Education and CEU's with Instant Certificates was the Frosting on the Cake!!, Donald J., RN, CEN, ANRP, Washington, DC._

_"I was searching for Spectrum and MyfreeCE and came across your site, amazing for Nursing CEU's free, RN.ORG is excellent! Free CEUs was my first thought and I ended up signing up before I even took the Free CEU course!". Robert B., RN, US Army_

_"Finding a Online Disaster Nursing Education website with CEU's for nurses that is so easy to use is incredible!! FEMA, Disaster, Bioterrorism and Nursing CEUs all on one site that are Accredited for Medics/Nurses by the state board of Nursing allows me more time to run my ER and less time dealing with education", JA P., RN, Los Angeles, CA_

_"Nursing CEUs are important for our license here here in Florida. Finding the right nursing CEU is the hard part, thank goodness for RN.ORG!", Robin A, LPN, Orlando, FL_

_"Wow, your system is so cool. I was looking for Free CEU Free Nursing Provider and found RN.ORG! I enjoy the ability to reprint my certificates and review my transcript at any time", Tony G., ANRP, Clinical Instructor, Miami, FL_

_"I was looking for a Free CEU Nursing Provider and Career Education Nursing and came upon RN.ORG!! Great information for the nurse as well for teaching our youth", Martha W., RN, Toronto, ON_

_"Very good source for Online Nursing Education and Nursing Contact Hours.. The content is something that all parents and healthcare workers can use", Rachelle U., LPN, Key Largo, FL_

_"Thanks for the Free Nursing CEU Course! You have become my Online RN Continuing Education Provider! I have since contacted my friends and now the whole floor is on RN.ORG! Learning with www.rn.org is so easy. I never knew taking nursing continuing education courses to obtain Free RN CEU could be so easy", Ronald G., RN, Washington, DC "_

_"Excellent Nursing Free CEU Provider! Thank you. Very well written. This was easy to read and was presented very well. The online free nursing CEU is excellent ", Robert E., RN, CEN, San Diego, CA_

_"Nursing CEU Courses Online from a CEU nursing Provider is so easy with RN.ORG!", Jason B., RN, Orlando, FL_

| 

**Privacy Policy**

At RN.org, we are committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning the use of that information.  Please read this policy carefully.  We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site.  We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone.

**The Information We Collect and How We Use**

We collect information on the site in order to make it possible for you to purchase items on our website and to enhance your overall experience.  We also monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve design and layout.  **RN.org will not collect personal information about you without your knowledge and consent.**

We may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and email, promotional activities, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service.  These RN.org agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.  Other than our outside agents, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so.  RN.org may also release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply the provisions of our _Terms of Service_ or to protect the rights, property or safety of RN.org, our users, or others.

RN.ORG may provide information in the aggregate to third parties without disclosure of personally identifying information.

**Transfers of Information**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets.  In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets.  Also, in the event that RN.org or substantially all of its assets are acquired, member information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Links**

Our site contains links from the sites of our advertisers, members of the healthcare industry and others.  RN.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of these linked sites.

**IP Address**

RN.org tracks IP (internet protocol) addresses for system administration purposes.  IP addresses are logged per user's session and help to determine how often areas on our site are visited.  However, RN.org does not track IP addresses with any of your personal information. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies to improve your experience on our website.  “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes.  We use cookies to remember information members give us so they don't have to reenter it each time they visit the site.  Cookies identify a user’s computer.  If you chose to decline cookies you will still be able to use most of the features on our website.

**Correcting or Updating Personal Information**

If the personal information we have gathered from you changes, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any data you have previously provided to us.  You may change your personal information at any time by accessing your “account info” page after logging in as a user and making the necessary changes.  We may retain a copy of the prior version for our records.

**Security of your information**

When you make a purchase on our website, the bank needs to obtain your credit card number, expiration date and billing address information.  This information is encrypted and transmitted safely over the internet to our bank where it is stored in their secure servers – where it is used for billing purposes only. RN.org does not have access to this information as all credit card processing is handled by our bank and is not stored on the RN.org servers.   Our bank uses SSL encryption to help ensure that all the personal information you provide is encrypted and remains private (unless sent by an unsecured means, such as email).  This helps to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

We strive to protect your personal information, however we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By visiting the RN.org site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of this information by RN.org.  We will always fully disclose our privacy policies, and we will promptly post any changes to our policy on this page.

You will have the time set forth in such notice to inform RN.org if you do not agree with the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you must inform RN.org and discontinue use of the RN.org website. 

You agree that RN.org may retain and use your personal information until you inform us that you do not agree with this Privacy Policy and agree that you will not use the RN.org website for a reasonable period of time thereafter, in accordance with RN.org 's data retention policies and/or practices.  By using this site after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes.

If you choose to visit RN.org, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

As a continuing education nursing provider, RN.org is interested in your professional articles which could be used as nursing continuing education online material. We provide all the credentialing and certifications using our provider numbers, you supply the content in a easy to read format with between 1800 and 2000 words in ideally, APA format. [Contact us](http://www.rn.org/AboutRNORG.php) for more information. [www.rn.org](http://www.rn.org/) is a continuing education provider nursing. 

|    
---|---
